Guide to the ACT UP New York records, 1969, 1982-1997 [bulk 1987-1995]
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series VII. Committees, 1985-1995, n.d.; 556287; 45 boxes
  - VII.C. Treatment and Data committee, 1986-1994, n.d.; 556717; 11 boxes
    - AIDS Clinical Trials, 556718
      - AIDS Clinical Trails Group (ACTG) meetings, 556719
        - Ninth, 1990 July; 556720 (Reel 46, Box 63, Folder 5)
        - Tenth: National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Disease, 1990 Nov; 556721 (Reel 46, Box 63, Folder 6)
        - Tenth: Report, circa 1990; 556722 (Reel 48, Box 65, Folder 1)
        - Eleventh, 1991 Mar 10-13; 556723 (Reel 46, Box 63, Folder 7)
        - Fourteenth: Report, 1992; 556724 (Reel 45, Box 62, Folder 9)
        - Fifteenth, 1992 Nov; 556725 (Reel 48, Box 65, Folder 3)
        - Sixteenth: National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Disease, 1993 Feb; 556726 (Reel 49, Box 66, Folder 1)
        - Seventeenth: National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Disease, 1993 Dec; 556727 (Reel 49, Box 66, Folder 2)
        - Summaries, 1991 Dec; 556728 (Reel 48, Box 65, Folder 2)
      - US Department of Health and Human Services. AIDS Clinical Trials Information Services (ACTIS): Selected Information on Open Clinical Trials, 1994; 556729 (Reel 49, Box 67, Folder 1-8)
    - Drug protocol studies, n.d.; 556730 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Drugs, 556731
      - AIDS/HIV Treatments, 556732
        - Acyclovir, n.d.; 556733 (Reel 50, Box 68, Folder 5)
        - Aerosolized pentamidine, n.d.; 556734 (Reel 50, Box 68, Folder 6)
        - AL 721, n.d.; 556735 (Reel 50, Box 68, Folder 7)
        - Alpha interferon, n.d.; 556736 (Reel 50, Box 68, Folder 8)
        - Ampligen, n.d.; 556737 (Reel 50, Box 68, Folder 9)
        - AZT, n.d.; 556738 (Reel 50, Box 68, Folder 10)
        - AZT, n.d.; 556739 (Reel 50, Box 69, Folder 1)
        - AZTG, n.d.; 556740 (Reel 50, Box 69, Folder 2)
        - B1-PG-587, n.d.; 556741 (Reel 50, Box 69, Folder 3)
        - Bactrim/Septa, n.d.; 556742 (Reel 50, Box 69, Folder 4)
        - Clarithromycin, n.d.; 556743 (Reel 50, Box 69, Folder 5)
        - CD4, n.d.; 556744 (Reel 50, Box 69, Folder 6)
        - Compound Q, 556745 (Reel 50, Box 69, Folder 7)
        - ddC, n.d.; 556746 (Reel 51, Box 69, Folder 12)
        - ddI+ddC, n.d.; 556747 (Reel 51, Box 69, Folder 8)
        - Dextran sulfate, n.d.; 556748 (Reel 51, Box 69, Folder 9)
        - Ditiocarb sodium, n.d.; 556749 (Reel 51, Box 69, Folder 10)
        - Doxil, 1993; 556750 (Reel 51, Box 69, Folder 11)
        - EPO, n.d.; 556751 (Reel 51, Box 69, Folder 13)
        - Fluconazole, n.d.; 556752 (Reel 51, Box 69, Folder 14)
        - Foscarnet, n.d.; 556753 (Reel 51, Box 69, Folder 15)
        - G-CSF, n.d.; 556754 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 1)
        - Gamma interferon, n.d.; 556755 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 2)
        - Ganciclovir (DHPG), n.d.; 556756 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 3-4)
        - HPMPC, 1993; 556757 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 5)
        - Hypericin, n.d.; 556758 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 6)
        - Ibogaine, n.d.; 556759 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 7)
        - IMREG-1, n.d.; 556760 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 8)
        - Imuthiol, n.d.; 556761 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 9)
        - Isoprinosine, n.d.; 556762 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 10)
        - Kemron, n.d.; 556763 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 11)
        - L661, n.d.; 556764 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 12)
        - Marijuana; MM-1, n.d.; 556765 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 13)
        - N-Acetylcysteine NAC, 556766 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 14)
        - Novapren, n.d.; 556767 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 15)
        - Pentamide, n.d.; 556768 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 16)
        - Peptide-T, n.d.; 556769 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 17)
        - Procysteine, n.d.; 556770 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 18)
        - Protocol 049, n.d.; 556771 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 19)
        - Ribavirin, n.d.; 556772 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 20)
        - Rifabutin, 1993; 556773 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 21)
        - Ritalin, n.d.; 556774 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 22)
        - SB-73, n.d.; 556775 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 23)
        - SP-PG, n.d.; 556776 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 24)
        - TLC G-65, n.d.; 556777 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 25)
        - Trental, n.d.; 556778 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 26)
        - TMP/SMX (Trimethoprim-Sulfamethoxazole), 1993; 556779 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 27)
        - Zovirax, n.d.; 556780 (Reel 51, Box 70, Folder 28)
      - General, n.d.; 556781 (Reel 52, Box 71, Folder 1-2)
      - Other reports, n.d.; 556782 (Reel 52, Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Unapproved by the FDA, 1990-1993; 556783 (Reel 49, Box 68, Folder 1-4)
    - Publications and near-print materials, 556784
      - ACT UP, 556785
        - Countdown 18 Months Plan, 1990 Nov; 556786 (Reel 45, Box 62, Folder 11)
        - Digest, 556787; Internal newsletter
          - 1989-1990, 556788 (Reel 44, Box 62, Folder 1-2)
          - 1991-1994, 556789 (Reel 45, Box 62, Folder 3-5)
        - Harrington, Mark. Critique of the AIDS Clinical Trails Group, 1990; 556790; Draft and final copy (Reel 45, Box 62, Folder 10)
        - Hernandez, Vic. AIDS 101. Basic Information, 556791 (Reel 52, Box 72, Folder 1)
        - T & D Handbook: Treatment Decisions, circa 1989, n.d.; 556792 (Reel 45, Box 63, Folder 1-2)
        - Treatment and Research] Agenda for Women with HIV Infection, 1991; 556793 (Reel 46, Box 63, Folder 3)
        - Update, 1989-1991; 556794; Internal newsletter (Reel 45, Box 62, Folder 6-8)
      - AIDS Treatment Registry, Inc. (ATR), 556795
        - Deciding to Enter an AIDS/HIV Drug Trial, 1989; 556796; Not microfilmed (Box 71, Folder 4-6)
        - Directory of AIDS/HIV Clinical Trials, New York and New Jersey, 1989; 556797; Not microfilmed; Draft (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases and the National Cancer Institute, 556798
        - MultiCenter AIDS Cohort Study, 556799
          - Volumes 1 and 2, 1991; 556800 (Reel 47, Box 64, Folder 1-5)
          - Volume 2, 1991; 556801 (Reel 48, Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Reports, 556802
        - Bahlman, Bill, et al. Summary of the US Health Summit on HIV Infection., 1988; 556803 (Reel 52, Box 72, Folder 2)
        - Bakeman, Roger. Changes in the Sexual Behavior of Gay Men: An Atlanta Survey., 1986; 556804 (Reel 52, Box 72, Folder 3)
        - Coullahan, Shawn, and Susan Thomas. Enhancement of Serial Learning with Lecithin., 1987; 556805 (Reel 52, Box 72, Folder 4)
        - Gay Men's Health Crisis. The Plan that Failed: An Evaluation of New York State's Five-Year Plan on AIDS., 1994 Jan; 556806 (Reel 52, Box 72, Folder 5)
        - Hadden, John W. Perspectives on the Immunotherapy of AIDS., n.d.; 556807 (Reel 52, Box 72, Folder 6)
        - Immtech International, Inc. Investigator's Brochure: C-Reactive Protein/Modified C-Reactive Protein., 1992 Jun 24; 556808 (Reel 53, Box 72, Folder 7-9)
        - Johns Hopkins University. SOCA [Studies of Ocular Complications of AIDS]: ACTG Protocol 129. CMV Retinitis Trial: Foscarnet Ganciclovir Component., 1990; 556809 (Reel 53, Box 72, Folder 10)
        - New York City Department of Health, AIDS Surveillance Unit. AIDS Surveillance Update., 1989 Apr 26; 556810 (Reel 53, Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Related material, n.d.; 556811 (Reel 46, Box 63, Folder 4)
- Series VIII. Subjects, 1982-1995, n.d.; 556812; 40 boxes
  Series VIII. Subjects is arranged alphabetically and includes a wide range of subjects related to AIDS/HIV. Subject headings are primarily those used by ACT UP. The materials in this series overlap with other series, especially the Committee series. The subjects themselves are not exclusive and overlap within this series and others. The bulk consists of newspaper articles along with some journal reports and broadsides. Subjects include, but are not limited to: AIDS education programs, confidentiality, and the impact of AIDS in Europe.
  - Abortion issues, 1991-1992; 556813 (Reel 55, Box 74, Folder 1)
  - ACT UP: Profiled, n.d.; 556814 (Reel 55, Box 74, Folder 2-5)
  - African Swine Fever, n.d.; 556815 (Reel 59, Box 78, Folder 9-10)
  - AIDS, 556816
    - General, 556817
      - 1987-1991, n.d., 556818 (Reel 55, Box 74, Folder 6-7)
      - The first decade, n.d.; 556819 (Reel 55, Box 74, Folder 8)
      - History of AIDS, n.d.; 556820 (Reel 55, Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Africa, n.d.; 556821 (Reel 59, Box 78, Folder 6-8)
    - AIDS Cure Project, n.d.; 556822; Formerly known as the Barbara McClintock Project to Cure AIDS. (Reel 56, Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Arts, n.d.; 556823; Folder 5 was not microfilmed. (Reel 55, Box 75, Folder 1-6)
    - Arts, n.d.; 556824 (Reel 56, Box 75, Folder 7-9)
    - Asia, n.d.; 556825 (Reel 56, Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Asia, n.d.; 556826 (Reel 60, Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Blacks and Hispanics, 556827 (Reel 60, Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Campaign, 1992; 556828 (Reel 56, Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Canada, n.d.; 556829 (Reel 60, Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Caribbean, n.d.; 556830 (Reel 60, Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Clinton/Gore, n.d.; 556831 (Reel 62, Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Conditions and drugs: Charts from George M. Carter, 1991-1993; 556832; See also Series VIII. Subjects: Carter, George M.: Charts. (Reel 56, Box 75, Folder 11-12)
    - Czar, 556833; Kristine Gebbie (Reel 56, Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Definition, n.d.; 556834 (Reel 56, Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Direct AIDS Alternative Information Resources (DAAIR), n.d.; 556835 (Reel 63, Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Discrimination, 1993; 556836 (Reel 56, Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Diseases, 556837
      - Other, 556838
        - 1992, 556839 (Reel 57, Box 77, Folder 2)
        - Articles on disease and treatments with some relevance to AIDS, circa 1991 Mar; 556840 (Reel 57, Box 77, Folder 1)
        - TB, 556841
          - 1992, 556842 (Reel 57, Box 76, Folder 11-13)
          - 1993, 556843 (Reel 57, Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Related, n.d.; 556844 (Reel 57, Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Division of AIDS Services, New York City, n.d.; 556845 (Reel 63, Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Education, 556846
      - n.d., 556847 (Reel 56, Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Programs, n.d.; 556848 (Reel 56, Box 76, Folder 7)
      - School board: New York Public Schools' "Rainbow" curriculum, 1993; 556849 (Reel 84, Box 107, Folder 1)
      - School, education, and AIDS, 556850 (Reel 84, Box 107, Folder 2-4)
      - School, education, and AIDS, 556851 (Reel 85, Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Europe, n.d.; 556852 (Reel 63, Box 83, Folder 12-14)
    - Famous people who have died, n.d.; 556853 (Reel 63, Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Global AIDS Policy Coalition, n.d.; 556854 (Reel 66, Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Global Summit on AIDS, 556855
      - undated, 556856 (Reel 66, Folder 88, Folder 14)
      - Media, n.d.; 556857 (Reel 66, Folder 88, Folder 15)
    - Harvard AIDS Institute, n.d.; 556858 (Reel 67, Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Heterosexuals, n.d.; 556859 (Reel 56, Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Heterosexuals, n.d.; 556860 (Reel 69, Box 91, Folder 8-9)
    - Hospitals, n.d.; 556861 (Reel 70, Box 92, Folder 8)
    - In the Workplace, 556862
      - n.d, 556863 (Reel 58, Box 78, Folder 3-4)
      - n.d, 556864 (Reel 59, Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Employment, n.d.; 556865 (Reel 90, Box 112, Folder 12)
    - India, 556866 (Reel 73, Box 95, Folder 2)
    - International impact, n.d.; 556867 (Reel 57, Box 76, Folder 9-10)
    - National Directory of AIDS Care Hotline, n.d.; 556868 (Reel 70, Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Neurological effects, n.d.; 556869 (Reel 76, Box 98, Folder 3)
    - People of Color, 556870
      - n.d, 556871 (Reel 80, Box 102, Folder 13-15)
      - n.d, 556872 (Reel 80, Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Conference, n.d.; 556873 (Reel 80, Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Politics, n.d.; 556874 (Reel 81, Box 103, Folder 9-14)
    - Presidential AIDS panel, n.d.; 556875 (Reel 81, Box 103, Folder 15-16)
    - Prisons, 1986-1989; 556876 (Reel 81, Box 104, Folder 4-7)
    - Prisons, 1990-1993; 556877 (Reel 82, Box 104, Folder 8-10)
    - Public, 556878
      - Health, n.d.; 556879 (Reel 82, Box 104, Folder 14-18)
      - Opinion, n.d.; 556880 (Reel 82, Box 105, Folder 1-5)
      - Opinion, n.d.; 556881 (Reel 83, Box 105, Folder 6-10)
    - Religion, n.d.; 556882 (Reel 83, Box 106, Folder 1-4)
    - Religion, n.d.; 556883 (Reel 84, Box 106, Folder 5-6)
    - Research: Federal budget cuts, circa 1992 Feb 26; 556884 (Reel 60, Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Researchers, n.d.; 556885 (Reel 58, Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Sexual abuse, n.d.; 556886 (Reel 58, Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Society, n.d.; 556887 (Reel 85, Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Soviet Union, n.d.; 556888 (Reel 85, Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Sports, n.d.; 556889 (Reel 85, Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Statistics, 1988-1991; 556890 (Reel 85, Box 107, Folder 12-15)
    - Testing, n.d.; 556891 (Reel 58, Box 77, Folder 7-9)
    - Theory, n.d.; 556892 (Reel 58, Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Transmission, 1982-1989; 556893 (Reel 88, Box 110, Folder 4-12)
    - Treatment, 556894
      - Drugs, n.d.; 556895 (Reel 86, Box 108, Folder 12-14)
      - Therapy, n.d.; 556896 (Reel 58, Box 77, Folder 11-15)
      - Therapy, n.d.; 556897 (Reel 58, Box 78, Folder 1-2)
    - World AIDS Day, 1992; 556898 (Reel 90, Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Zaire, n.d.; 556899 (Reel 90, Box 112, Folder 15)
  - American Federation of Labor, n.d.; 556900 (Reel 59, Box 79, Folder 1)
  - American Foundation for AIDS Research (AmFAR), 556901 (Reel 59, Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Anti-viral drugs, n.d.; 556902 (Reel 59, Box 79, Folder 3-8)
  - Ashe, Arthur, n.d.; 556903 (Reel 59, Box 79, Folder 9)
  - ASTRA, n.d.; 556904 (Reel 60, Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Bias/Discrimination, n.d.; 556905 (Reel 60, Box 79, Folder 12-14)
  - Blood and blood banks, 556906 (Reel 60, Box 80, Folder 1-4)
  - Blue Cross rate increases, 1995 Feb 22; 556907 (Reel 60, Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Board of Education, 1992; 556908 (Reel 60, Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Bomb threats, 1993 Jul 20-Aug 11, Oct 15; 556909; Not microfilmed (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Boycott Colorado, 1992 Dec-1993 Jan, circa Mar 13; 556910 (Reel 60, Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Bristol-Myers Squibb, n.d.; 556911 (Reel 60, Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Bush/Quayle, 1992; 556912; Regarding the presidential debates (Reel 60, Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Campaign, 1992; 556913 (Reel 60, Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Campbell's bill, n.d.; 556914; A bill, H.R. 2872, sponsored by Rep. Tom Campbell to expedite the FDA approval of drugs for certain diseases.; Correspondence and related material (Reel 60, Box 80, Folder 13-14)
  - Carter, George M.: Charts, 1991-1992, 1993 Jun 2; 556915; See also Series VIII. Subjects, AIDS: Conditions and Drugs: Charts from George M. Carter 1991-1993. (Reel 61, Box 80, Folder 17-18)
  - Catholic church, n.d.; 556916 (Reel 61, Box 81, Folder 1-5)
  - Caucus to House Homeless People with AIDS, n.d.; 556917 (Reel 61, Box 81, Folder 6-8)
  - Center on Addiction and Substance Abuse (CASA), 556918 (Reel 62, Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Centers for Disease Control (CDC), 556919
    - n.d, 556920 (Reel 61, Box 81, Folder 9)
    - National AIDS clearinghouse, n.d.; 556921 (Reel 61, Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Working group, n.d.; 556922 (Reel 61, Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Church Ladies Action, 1993; 556923 (Reel 62, Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Civil disobedience, 556924
    - n.d, 556925 (Reel 62, Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Training, n.d.; 556926 (Reel 62, Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Cleveland, 556927; Site for the Democratic platform hearings (Reel 62, Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Clinton, 556928
    - Cabinet, 1992; 556929 (Reel 62, Folder 82, Folder 9)
    - Pledge -- ACT UP New York, n.d.; 556930; ACT UP New York member pledges to confront President Clinton regarding AIDS issues whenever he visits New York. (Reel 62, Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Post-election, 1992; 556931 (Reel 62, Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Coalition for the Homeless, n.d.; 556932 (Reel 62, Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Colorado, 556933
    - Cemetery case, n.d.; 556934 (Reel 62, Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Health issues, n.d.; 556935 (Reel 62, Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Condom use (education/prevention), 1992-1993; 556936 (Reel 62, Box 82, Folder 13-14)
  - Confidentiality issues, 1989-1994, n.d.; 556937 (Reel 62, Box 82, Folder 15-19)
  - Democratic National Convention 1992, 556938
    - ACT UP broadsides, 1992; 556939 (Reel 63, Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1992; 556940 (Reel 63, Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings and news releases, 1992; 556941 (Reel 63, Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Disclosure issues: Mandatory testing, 1993; 556942 (Reel 63, Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Discrimination, n.d.; 556943 (Reel 63, Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Domestic partner plans, n.d.; 556944 (Reel 63, Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Drugs, 556945
    - Recreational, n.d.; 556946 (Reel 83, Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Use reports, 556947
      - n.d, 556948 (Reel 63, Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Court cases, n.d.; 556949 (Reel 63, Box 83, Folder 11)
      - News clippings, n.d.; 556950 (Reel 63, Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Euthanasia, n.d.; 556951; Article (Reel 63, Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), 1990-1995; 556952 (Reel 64, Box 84, Folder 10-11)
  - Federal government: Miscellaneous, 1983, 1987-1988, 1990; 556953 (Reel 63, Box 84, Folder 2-6)
  - Federal government: Miscellaneous, 1990-1992; 556954 (Reel 64, Box 84, Folder 7-9)
  - Fetal tissue research, n.d.; 556955 (Reel 65, Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Fight for Life Committee, n.d.; 556956; An AIDS activist organization in North Lauderdale, Florida. (Reel 65, Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Food and Drug Administration (FDA), 556957
    - 1987-1988, 556958 (Reel 64, Box 85, Folder 1)
    - 1989-1992, n.d., 556959 (Reel 64, Box 85, Folder 3-6)
    - Demonstration, 1988 Oct 10; 556960 (Reel 64, Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising, 556961
    - Angels in America, circa 1993 May 27; 556962; Not microfilmed (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Contact, n.d.; 556963 (Reel 65, Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Gay, 556964
    - Men: Issues, n.d.; 556965 (Reel 66, Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Organizations, n.d.; 556966 (Reel 66, Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Pride parade, 1988-1995; 556967; Documentation of annual celebrations in June of each year listed. Folder 3, Gay Pride 1988, was not microfilmed. (Reel 66, Box 88, Folder 3-8)
    - Rights: New York State Assembly, 1993; 556968 (Reel 66, Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Gay and Lesbian, 556969
    - Bibliography, n.d.; 556970 (Reel 65, Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Events, n.d.; 556971 (Reel 65, Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Issues, 1990; 556972 (Reel 65, Box 86, Folder 7-9)
    - Issues, 1990-1991; 556973 (Reel 65, Box 87, Folder 1-5)
    - Issues, 1991-1992; 556974; Folder 7 contains documents relating to the City Council election campaigns of two openly gay candidates, Thomas Duane, who was also HIV+, and Liz Abzug. Folder 8 contains documents concerning the murder/hate crime of Julio Rivera dating from Oct. 1991. (Reel 66, Box 87, Folder 6-9)
  - Geffen, David, 556975 (Reel 66, Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Glasser, Elizabeth, n.d.; 556976 (Reel 66, Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Global contacts, n.d.; 556977 (Reel 66, Box 88, Folder 13)
  - God's Love We Deliver, n.d.; 556978; An organization that provides meals for homebound people with AIDS, cancer, and other serious illnesses. (Reel 66, Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Golden Gate, n.d.; 556979; ACT UP Golden Gate (Reel 66, Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Graphics, n.d.; 556980 (Reel 67, Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Grief counseling, n.d.; 556981 (Reel 66, Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Guantanamo Bay/Haiti, 1993; 556982 (Reel 66, Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Guantanamo Bay/Haiti, 1993; 556983 (Reel 67, Box 89, Folder 3,5)
  - Hate and antagonistic mail, 556984 (Reel 67, Box 89, Folder 10-15)
  - Hate crimes, 1992-1993; 556985 (Reel 67, Box 89, Folder 7-8)
  - Hate Crimes Coalition, n.d.; 556986 (Reel 67, Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Healthcare, 556987
    - Access and plans, 556988 (Reel 67, Box 90, Folder 1-3)
    - Access and plans, 556989 (Reel 68, Box 90, Folder 4-8)
    - Hospitals, 1992; 556990 (Reel 68, Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Hospitalization, n.d.; 556991 (Reel 70, Box 92, Folder 6-7)
    - National/universal healthcare update, n.d.; 556992 (Reel 68, Box 91, Folder 1-2)
    - US Department of Health and Human Services, 556993 (Reel 69, Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Workers and AIDS, 556994 (Reel 69, Box 91, Folder 4-5)
  - Hemophilia action, Hotel Macklowe, New York City, n.d.; 556995 (Reel 69, Box 91, Folder 6)
  - HIV treatment, n.d.; 556996 (Reel 69, Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Hoffman La Roche action, n.d.; 556997 (Reel 69, Box 91, Folder 10-13)
  - Holland, 556998 (Reel 69, Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Homeopathy, n.d.; 556999 (Reel 69, Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Homophobia, 1992; 557000 (Reel 70, Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Hoover, J. Edgar, n.d.; 557001 (Reel 70, Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Housing, 557002
    - n.d, 557003 (Reel 70, Folder 92, Folder 10)
    - n.d, 557004 (Reel 71, Folder 93, Folder 1-5)
    - Arrest sheets, n.d.; 557005 (Reel 71, Folder 93, Folder 6)
    - Department of Housing Preservation, n.d.; 557006 (Reel 71, Folder 93, Folder 7-9)
    - Homeless, n.d.; 557007 (Reel 70, Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Human rights issues, 557008
    - Amnesty International, 557009
      - n.d, 557010 (Reel 72, Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Handbook, 557011 (Reel 72, Box 94, Folder 2)
      - USA, n.d.; 557012 (Reel 71, Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Human Rights Watch, 557013 (Reel 72, Box 94, Folder 4)
    - New York City Commission on Human Rights, n.d.; 557014 (Reel 72, Box 94, Folder 5)
    - United Nations, n.d.; 557015 (Reel 72, Box 94, Folder 6-8)
    - World AIDS Day, 1992; 557016 (Reel 72, Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d.; 557017 (Reel 72, Box 94, Folder 10-11)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d.; 557018 (Reel 72, Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Insurance, n.d.; 557019 (Reel 73, Box 95, Folder 6-8)
  - International Gay Issues: Stonewall 25, circa 1994 Jun; 557020 (Reel 73, Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Inter-religious Foundation for Community Organization, 557021 (Reel 73, Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Intravenous (IV) Drug, 557022
    - Use, n.d.; 557023 (Reel 73, Box 95, Folder 9-11)
    - Users, n.d.; 557024 (Reel 73, Box 95, Folder 12-14)
  - Irish Lesbian Gay Organization (ILGO), 1992; 557025 (Reel 73, Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, Magic, n.d.; 557026 (Reel 74, Box 96, Folder 1-4)
  - Kaposi's sarcoma, n.d.; 557027 (Reel 74, Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Kramer, Larry, n.d.; 557028 (Reel 74, Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Kessler, David, n.d.; 557029 (Reel 74, Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Legal issues, n.d.; 557030 (Reel 74, Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Legalize marijuana movement, n.d.; 557031 (Reel 74, Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Lesbian AIDS Project (LAP) and related material, 557032; A program of the Gay Men's Health Crisis [GMHC]. (Reel 74, Box 96, Folder 10)
  - March on Washington, 1993; 557033 (Reel 74, Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Marshall training tips, n.d.; 557034 (Reel 74, Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Media, 557035
    - People with AIDS issues, n.d.; 557036 (Reel 74, Box 97, Folder 1)
    - People with AIDS issues, n.d.; 557037 (Reel 75, Box 97, Folder 2-13)
    - Police brutality, 1991-1992; 557038 (Reel 81, Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Merck and Company, 557039; Concerns a possible HIV vaccine developed by the pharmaceutical company. (Reel 74, Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Military ban on gays, 1993; 557040 (Reel 74, Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Miller beer boycott, 557041
    - n.d, 557042 (Reel 74, Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Helms articles, n.d.; 557043 (Reel 74, Box 96, Folder 15)
  - National Institutes of Health (NIH), 557044
    - n.d, 557045 (Reel 76, Box 98, Folder 1)
    - National Cancer Institute, n.d.; 557046 (Reel 76, Box 98, Folder 2)
  - New York City, 557047
    - 1988, 557048 (Reel 77, Box 99, Folder 8)
    - 1989-1990, 557049 (Reel 78, Box 100, Folder 1-3)
    - AIDS czar, n.d.; 557050; Ronald Johnson (Reel 78, Box 100, Folder 4)
    - AIDS issues, n.d.; 557051 (Reel 76, Box 98, Folder 4-7)
    - Budget crisis, 1991 May-Jul; 557052 (Reel 76, Box 98, Folder 8-10)